<ObjectTemplate>
  <Name>History of Celador: Part 1</Name>
	<ClientId>1346</ClientId>
	<SharedStateEntry name="Weight" type="int" value="-1"/>
	<ObjectVariableComponent/>	
	<ScriptEngineComponent>
		<LuaModule Name="book">
			<Initializer>
				{ 
				Text = "Complete History of Celador: Part 1\n\nChapter 1: Pre-History:\n\nVery little is known about the time before recorded history, before the first written records in Aria. At one time, during an era countless years ago, dragons ruled over all of Aria, and over Celador. It was only after a great calamity did the Dragon Age end, the likes of which are not known, but a thin layer of dragonglass (above which dragon bones are rarely found), covers the entire world and that shows the difference between older and newer stone. Countless ages later, man appeared on Aria, and little is known about his wereabouts, or the reason for his arrival.  What we do know is that in this age, the Gods known as the Strangers supposedly ruled, appearing on Aria no earlier than 10,000 years before this writing, and vanished no later than 4,000 years. Almost no records or artifacts survive from this age aside from the Dead Gate and the Relics, but what is known is that man was said to have been barbaric, brutal, and stupid, civilized by the Strangers who little is known about, including their apperance except for ancient folklore claiming them to be ten feet tall, with boundless wisdom and mighty power. According to legend at some point, the Strangers left, supposedly leaving a single man to rule all of Aria, the First King. However, the people revolted, and Aria slid back into barbarism. According to ancient books that pre-date the Destruction of Aria, not a single city was found from this age at all, nor artifact, or building, or writing or anything. This supposed story of the First King would widely be considered myth and legend were it not for the Dead Gate that dates back to that time period, and it's story as fact or fiction is controversial at the time of this writing.\n\nChapter 2: First Age of Man\n\nAt this time, it is believed than the first men with writing, the Ulaats arrived in Celador from the Great Sea that exists to the north-east of the Outlands, bringing with him the worship of the Ancient Gods Lilith and Eve. Other scholars say that the Ulaats were here since the building of the Dead Gate, and their ancestors built it themselves. Regardless the Ulaats tribes were the first people to leave written records and the beginning of Celador proper. For a thousand years of so the Ulaat tribes fought and lived in what is now Celador until the Phoneosians, that which is commonly known as the Artificers by ships from across the sea, conquering and enslaving the Ulaats for their own purposes. The Phoneosians, had a mighty seagoing empire that spanned a good portion of Aria, and were native to a desert region that early books claim to have been a thousand leagues from Celador at that time. Building a great city that spanned most of Celador the Phoneosians ruins still stand today, some 3,000 years after their construction. Little is known about them as well, except for a legend that they learned dark magic that consumed their civilization in a single night. Now the Ruins of the Artificers are a lifeless desert, in stark contrast from the rest of Celador. \n\nThe Phoneosians believed in several Gods, in addition to that of Lilith and Eve. Some claim that it is the remains of the Stranger-Worship from pre-history, others say they worshiped the Gods that the Cultists now worship. Regardless the Phoneosians were crafty engineers, able to work all kinds of metal and stone, and had a king who ruled over all their lands. In the aftermath of their dissapearance, the remaining people who lived in Celador became pastroal farmers, speaking a dialect of Phoneosian that is now extinct, but did not practice writing so little is known about the dark age that follows. \n\nChapter 3: The Boundless Age\n\nAfter this time, it is believed that before the arrival of the descendents of the founders of Petra, Celador was conquered and inhabitted by several successive empires and kingdoms, and inhabited by various peoples. Even less is known about this time leading up to the Destruction of Aria, but it is said that mankind were masters of all things and rivalling the gods, creating carts that could move themselves, and weapons that could kill a man with fire and lead. However what is known is that during this time, that of Cleon the Builder arrived. Seeking independence from the Kingdom of Wesslton, yet another nameless, untracable conquering nation, Cleon founded the city of Petra on a spot of cleared land, and became it's first mayor. All was well and Petra came to claim many as it's inhabitants, until the kings's jealousy lead him to attempt to attack Petra and Celador, leading to the founding of the Guardian Order, the Building of the Wall, and the creation of a republic. Eventually the king was fought off, but that precipitated the arrival of the next biggest threat to that of Celador - the Cult of the Star Dweller. Some two centuries after this war, at the height of mankind's prowless, a man by the name of Degodad Kommen, a chieftan and shaman of the tribes of the far off Eastern Steppe claimed to have seen visions of gods so old, and so powerful, that mankind was purposeless without them. He claimed that the end of the world was arriving, and that mankind needed to submit itself to the whim of what we now call the Elder Gods. Claming that the end of the world was at hand, Kommen assembled a massive army and began conquering city after city, converting countless millions to his cause. After suffering several defeats, a small branch of this religion retreated into Celador, settling in the Ruins of the Artificers and claming it was the work of the Elder Gods they so worshipped. Eventually, for reasons unknown to man and at the climax of the war, the world did end, and the Destruction of Aria isolated Celador and the Outlands from the rest of Aria. It is often claimed that so powerful was mankind that he was unable to control his power, until even the Gods themselves became jealous and destroyed Aria.  Since the Destruction of Aria, stories of people arriving from other parts of Aria circulated but became dismissed as rumors, and few are actually known to have traveled magically from one portion of Aria to another. \n\nEnd of Part 1"
				}
			</Initializer>
		</LuaModule>
	</ScriptEngineComponent>
</ObjectTemplate>