<ObjectTemplate>
  <Name>[00FF00]Book Of Khutnartash[-]</Name>
	<ClientId>113</ClientId>
	<SharedStateEntry name="Weight" type="int" value="1"/>
	<ObjectVariableComponent/>	
	<ScriptEngineComponent>
		<LuaModule Name="note">
			<Initializer>
				{ 
				Text = "Praise be memory of Khutnartash, the ancient God who was from the stock of the Old Ones, a truely corrupt and vile God, a representation and example to be set for all those who know the truth of the coming of Desolation upon the world. When he set foot on the world, he spoke nothing but hatred and death arrived where he wandered. \n\nFor Khutnartash was the one who came to this world, knowing only what the Gods know, blessed be their name. He knew the magics, and knew the witchcraft, and knew the sorcerery of all things, and inquired about them frequently upon the land. \n\nLet it be known for all posterity that he desired nothing more than to know the progress of the people of Aria. It is to surmise that he desired us to wield the power of lightning, as he inquried on it more frequently than not. Blessed be his memory, cursed be the tales of his compassion or lack of discipline, those may not be known to any who seeks the true path. For all know that the Dead Gods are hate, sin, and death incarnate, and anyone who Blasphemies against such shall know their wrath. \n\nWe are the weapons of the Ancient Ones, and that we shall destroy all who oppose them. We are the members of the true path, the darkened ones, and we shall prevail agaisnt all those who decieve. \n\nLet me now warn you the punishments to be metteded against blasphemiers, and those who disobey their lord and priest. \n\nFor the crime of heresy, the sword is to be blunt, and a chopping of all limbs followed by feasting on their flesh for their crime should be given. Leave the man to die in a river, to be eaten by the crocodile and the fish. \n\nFor the crime of blasphemy, the man must be stuck to a pillar, and clubs must be gathered for all those who heard him utter it. This man must be beaten until all parts of his body paraded through the temple, and then branded on his forehead, to let all know his crime. \n\nFor disobedience, a whipping will be the punishment, the number of lashes to be determined by his superior. \n\nFor theft against the followers of the True Religion, know that it is not to be punished if one of three things are known: \n\nThe victim is a blasphemer, heretic, or coward. \nThe victim is known to be weak or incompetent, a slave, or a prostitute. \nThe victim is not the superior of the other, or not able to defeat the other in combat. \n\nTrial of such shall be a fight to the death, the winner takes all. \n\nFor the crime of traitors, they are to be disembowled, and then torn apart by the dogs. \n\nFor the crime of incompetence, they are to be struck in the head by a fist. \n\nFor the crime of failure, in the case of war, or combat, they are to be beheaded, or mocked, the former for the former, and the latter for the latter. \n\nKnow these punishments are to be extended or reduced based on the opinion of thy lord, or thy priest."
				}
			</Initializer>
		</LuaModule>
	</ScriptEngineComponent>
</ObjectTemplate>